EDUCATION

- Systems Engineering
 Universidad Nacional de Colombia
 2017-2023
- Academic Bachelor
 Colegio Cooperativo Monseñor
 Ismael Perdomo
 2013

SKILLS

| Frontend Development |
|------------------------|
| AngularJS |
| Angular Material |
| Responsive Design |
| Javascript |
| Typescript |
| HTML |
| SCSS |
| Git |
| ReactJS |
| |
| Unit Testing (Jasmine) |

CONTACT



(+57) 310 4812984



baorozcoc@unal.edu.co

Berny Alejandro Orozco Córdoba

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Hello, I'm Berny Alejandro Orozco, a passionate Software and Web Frontend Developer with a keen interest in UX and UI design. I'm currently expanding my skill set by learning various frameworks, aiming to a masters degree and motivated to create intuitive and engaging digital experiences. My expertise extends to illustration and graphical design, which allows me to bring a unique, artistic perspective to my work. I believe in the power of design and technology to solve complex problems and strive to create solutions that are not only functional but also aesthetically pleasing.

EXPERIENCE

Angular Developer

Teclogi

January 2023 - Present

- Design, develop, test and deploy new features
- Improve the responsive design of the platform
- Improve the UI/UX of the platform
- Implement improvements at the code level
- Apply best practices
- Provide support to company members

Assistant Student - React Developer

Universidad Nacional de Colombia.

January 2023 - June 2023

- Develop, test and deploy new features with tight delivery times
- Follow up with the client(students) to improve existing features
- Improve the responsive design of the platform
- Apply best practices
- Platform maintenance and bug tracking